Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
(This is a work of fiction)
(هذا عمل خيالي)
Get up. We're going out.
انهض، نحن سنخرج.
Where are we going?
إلى أين نحن ذاهبون؟
Didn't you say you wanted to test the projection?
ألم تقل أنك تريد اختبار العرض؟
This one, right?
هذا واحد، أليس كذلك؟
This is the one.
هذا هو.
We're buying it.
نحن نشتريه.
That's it?
هذا كل شيء؟
Let's go home and watch the projection.
دعونا نذهب إلى المنزل ونشاهد العرض.
If it changes, that means we passed this level.
إذا تغير فهذا يعني أننا تجاوزنا هذا المستوى.
And my guess is right.
وتخميني صحيح.
Not bad, Chen Jia Wen.
ليس سيئا، تشين جيا وين.
I told you already.
لقد أخبرتك بالفعل.
I'm a genius.
أنا عبقري.
Let's quickly see how to pass the next level.
دعونا نرى بسرعة كيفية اجتياز المستوى التالي.
I really want to put you in my pocket.
أريد حقًا أن أضعك في جيبي.
Then wherever I go, I can take you with me.
ثم أينما أذهب، أستطيع أن آخذك معي.
Then you'll get tired of me very quickly.
ثم سوف تشعر بالملل مني بسرعة كبيرة.
Never.
أبداً.
Chen Jia Wen,
تشن جيا ون,
I advise you to mind your words from now on.
أنصحك بأن تنتبه لكلماتك من الآن فصاعدا.
You're always running your mouth.
أنت تتحدث كثيرا دائما.
You're blaming me again.
أنت تلومني مرة أخرى.
Look how happy you were smiling.
أنظر إلى مدى سعادتك عندما ابتسمت.
What should we do next?
ماذا يجب علينا أن نفعل بعد ذلك؟
Become conjoined twins?
تصبح توأم ملتصق؟
Haven't you noticed that we've been holding hands...
ألم تلاحظ أننا كنا نمسك بأيدينا...
since we woke up?
منذ أن استيقظنا؟
Don't be nervous.
لا تكن عصبيا.
Listen to me. This level is the easiest.
اسمع لي، هذا المستوى هو الأسهل.
Let's lie in bed all day today.
دعونا نستلقي في السرير طوال اليوم.
Then we'll pass this level.
ثم سنجتاز هذا المستوى.
No way... I'm not mentally prepared yet.
لا يمكن... أنا لست مستعدًا عقليًا بعد.
Let's pass this level another day.
دعونا نتجاوز هذا المستوى في يوم آخر.
See?
يرى؟
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
It resets once we don't hold hands?
هل يتم إعادة ضبطه عندما لا نمسك بأيدينا؟
Are we...
هل نحن...
going to stay like this for a day?
هل ستبقى هكذا ليوم واحد؟
What's wrong with staying with me for a day?
ما المشكلة في البقاء معي ليوم واحد؟
I got it.
حصلت عليه.
If you stay with me for a day, you won't be able...
إذا بقيت معي ليوم واحد، فلن تكون قادرًا على...
to see your little lover, right?
لرؤية حبيبك الصغير، أليس كذلك؟
What little lover?
ما هذا العاشق الصغير؟
You've already made it official on social media.
لقد قمت بالفعل بإعلان ذلك رسميًا على وسائل التواصل الاجتماعي.
I saw it.
لقد رأيته.
We broke up, so I don't mind.
لقد انفصلنا، لذلك لا يهمني.
You really keep up with my updates.
أنت حقا تواكب التحديثات الخاصة بي.
I just accidentally saw it,
لقد رأيته بالصدفة
okay?
تمام؟
Besides,
بجانب،
I'm quite curious about your new boyfriend.
أنا فضولي جدًا بشأن صديقك الجديد.
Come on, let me meet him.
تعال، دعني أقابله.
Fine.
بخير.
It doesn't matter anyway.
لا يهم على أية حال.
You're quite open.
أنت منفتح تماما.
- Let's go. - Come on.
- دعنا نذهب. - هيا.
Welcome.
مرحباً.
Sit wherever you want.
اجلس أينما تريد.
Let's sit here.
دعنا نجلس هنا.
Hello.
مرحبًا.
Enjoy.
يتمتع.
That's him?
هذا هو؟
Your little lover?
حبيبك الصغير؟
What little lover?
ما هذا العاشق الصغير؟
What are you talking about?
ماذا تتحدث عنه؟
Stop pretending.
توقف عن التظاهر.
Look at the way he stares at you...
أنظر إلى الطريقة التي ينظر إليك بها...
with those smoldering eyes.
مع تلك العيون المشتعلة.
Hello.
مرحبًا.
This is our newly-released item.
هذا هو العنصر الذي تم إصداره حديثًا.
We're giving it to our customers for free.
نحن نقدمها لعملائنا مجانًا.
Stop right there.
توقف هنا.
I'm still here.
أنا لا أزال هنا.
How dare you draw a heart for her?
كيف تجرؤ على رسم قلب لها؟
Am I too nice to you?
هل أنا لطيف معك أكثر من اللازم؟
Are you crazy, Chen Jia Wen?
هل أنت مجنونة، تشين جيا وين؟
Answer my question first.
أجب على سؤالي أولا.
Did you two get together long ago?
هل التقيتم منذ زمن طويل؟
No.
لا.
No?
لا؟
Then why would he look at you like that?
إذن لماذا ينظر إليك بهذه الطريقة؟
I was still there.
كنت لا أزال هناك.
We were even holding hands.
حتى أننا كنا نمسك بأيدينا.
I can't be bothered to explain.
لا أستطيع أن أزعج نفسي بالشرح.
Act.
يمثل.
Just put on an act.
مجرد تمثيل.
No.
لا.
I'll make you stop acting.
سأجعلك تتوقف عن التمثيل.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Where are we going?
إلى أين نحن ذاهبون؟
Welcome.
مرحباً.
Wait. What are you doing?
انتظر ماذا تفعل؟
Can't you see this lady isn't willing?
ألا ترى أن هذه السيدة ليست راغبة؟
Can't you see this?
ألا ترى هذا؟
I don't care what your relationship is.
لا يهمني ما هي علاقتك.
As long as this lady is unwilling,
ما دامت هذه السيدة غير راغبة،
you can't force her.
لا يمكنك إجبارها.
Who are you to teach me?
من أنت لتعلميني؟
Look at you.
أنظر إليك.
You can't keep acting, can you?
لا يمكنك الاستمرار في التمثيل، أليس كذلك؟
I caught you, didn't I?
لقد أمسكت بك، أليس كذلك؟
You actually bit me to save him.
لقد عضضتني في الواقع لإنقاذه.
Why should you hit him?
لماذا يجب عليك ضربه؟
What did he do wrong?
ماذا فعل خطأ؟
You're mad now?
هل أنت مجنون الآن؟
He just fell in love with me at first sight.
لقد وقع في حبي من النظرة الأولى.
How often does love at first sight happen?
كم مرة يحدث الحب من النظرة الأولى؟
Didn't you fall in love with me at first sight?
ألم تقع في حبي من النظرة الأولى؟
You don't believe me, right?
أنت لا تصدقني، أليس كذلك؟
Fine.
بخير.
I'll prove it to you.
سأثبت لك ذلك.
Just wait.
فقط انتظر.
He confesses every time.
ويعترف في كل مرة.
If he doesn't confess today,
إذا لم يعترف اليوم،
won't we have waited for nothing?
ألا ننتظر شيئا؟
He'll surely do it.
سوف يفعل ذلك بالتأكيد.
If I didn't happen...
لو لم يحدث...
to like the scenery here,
أحب المناظر الطبيعية هنا،
I wouldn't believe...
لا أستطيع أن أصدق...
that there's someone in this world...
أن هناك شخص ما في هذا العالم...
who can love me...
من يستطيع أن يحبني...
no matter what I look like.
بغض النظر عن مظهري.
(Being unhappy isn't allowed in this place)
(لا يُسمح بالتعاسة في هذا المكان)
It doesn't matter if I don't know his name.
لا يهم إذا كنت لا أعرف اسمه.
It doesn't matter if we don't have a future.
لا يهم إذا لم يكن لدينا مستقبل.
All I want...
كل ما أريده...
is this moment...
هل هذه اللحظة...
of being firmly chosen by him.
أن يتم اختياره بقوة من قبله.
This is the feeling Chen Jia Wen hasn't given me in a long time.
هذا هو الشعور الذي لم يمنحه لي تشين جيا وين منذ وقت طويل.
You've miscalculated.
لقد أخطأت في حساباتك.
He has no intention of confessing at all.
ليس لديه أي نية للاعتراف على الإطلاق.
Let's wait some more.
دعونا ننتظر أكثر.
Wait some more? We've been waiting all day.
انتظر أكثر؟ لقد انتظرنا طوال اليوم.
I've run out of patience. Let's go.
لقد نفد صبري. هيا بنا.
Just be honest with me.
فقط كن صادقا معي.
We've already broken up. What can I do to you?
لقد انفصلنا بالفعل. ماذا يمكنني أن أفعل لك؟
I like you.
أنا معجب بك.
From the moment you walked in,
منذ اللحظة التي دخلت فيها،
I've liked you.
لقد اعجبت بك.
You don't have to respond.
لا داعي للرد.
You don't have to feel burdened either.
لا داعي لأن تشعر بالثقل أيضًا.
I just...
انا فقط...
want to tell you.
أريد أن أخبرك.
I'm sorry, sir.
انا آسف سيدي.
I know this is very presumptuous of me.
أعرف أن هذا تصرف متهور للغاية مني.
But I thought if I...
ولكنني اعتقدت أنه إذا...
don't say it today,
لا تقل ذلك اليوم
I might never get the chance to say it again.
ربما لن أحصل على فرصة لأقولها مرة أخرى.
See?
يرى؟